{
  "questions": [
    {
      "question": "Which is the most popular JavaScript framework?",
      "options": [
        "Angular",
        "React",
        "Svelte",
        "Vue"
      ],
      "correctOption": 1,
      "points": 10,
      "id": "d6b2"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which company invented React?",
      "options": [
        "Google",
        "Apple",
        "Netflix",
        "Facebook"
      ],
      "correctOption": 3,
      "points": 10,
      "id": "f085"
    },
    {
      "question": "What's the fundamental building block of React apps?",
      "options": [
        "Components",
        "Blocks",
        "Elements",
        "Effects"
      ],
      "correctOption": 0,
      "points": 10,
      "id": "a47f"
    },
    {
      "question": "What's the name of the syntax we use to describe the UI in React components?",
      "options": [
        "FBJ",
        "Babel",
        "JSX",
        "ES2015"
      ],
      "correctOption": 2,
      "points": 10,
      "id": "2f4f"
    },
    {
      "question": "How does data flow naturally in React apps?",
      "options": [
        "From parents to children",
        "From children to parents",
        "Both ways",
        "The developers decides"
      ],
      "correctOption": 0,
      "points": 10,
      "id": "de2b"
    },
    {
      "question": "How to pass data into a child component?",
      "options": [
        "State",
        "Props",
        "PropTypes",
        "Parameters"
      ],
      "correctOption": 1,
      "points": 10,
      "id": "514f"
    },
    {
      "question": "When to use derived state?",
      "options": [
        "Whenever the state should not trigger a re-render",
        "Whenever the state can be synchronized with an effect",
        "Whenever the state should be accessible to all components",
        "Whenever the state can be computed from another state variable"
      ],
      "correctOption": 3,
      "points": 30,
      "id": "eef6"
    },
    {
      "question": "What triggers a UI re-render in React?",
      "options": [
        "Running an effect",
        "Passing props",
        "Updating state",
        "Adding event listeners to DOM elements"
      ],
      "correctOption": 2,
      "points": 20,
      "id": "8319"
    },
    {
      "question": "When do we directly \"touch\" the DOM in React?",
      "options": [
        "When we need to listen to an event",
        "When we need to change the UI",
        "When we need to add styles",
        "Almost never"
      ],
      "correctOption": 3,
      "points": 20,
      "id": "4d0e"
    },
    {
      "question": "In what situation do we use a callback to update state?",
      "options": [
        "When updating the state will be slow",
        "When the updated state is very data-intensive",
        "When the state update should happen faster",
        "When the new state depends on the previous state"
      ],
      "correctOption": 3,
      "points": 30,
      "id": "3459"
    },
    {
      "question": "If we pass a function to useState, when will that function be called?",
      "options": [
        "On each re-render",
        "Each time we update the state",
        "Only on the initial render",
        "The first time we update the state"
      ],
      "correctOption": 2,
      "points": 30,
      "id": "e1f0"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which hook to use for an API request on the component's initial render?",
      "options": [
        "useState",
        "useEffect",
        "useRef",
        "useReducer"
      ],
      "correctOption": 1,
      "points": 10,
      "id": "8fe7"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which variables should go into the useEffect dependency array?",
      "options": [
        "Usually none",
        "All our state variables",
        "All state and props referenced in the effect",
        "All variables needed for clean up"
      ],
      "correctOption": 2,
      "points": 30,
      "id": "741e"
    },
    {
      "question": "An effect will always run on the initial render.",
      "options": [
        "True",
        "It depends on the dependency array",
        "False",
        "In depends on the code in the effect"
      ],
      "correctOption": 0,
      "points": 30,
      "id": "8300"
    },
    {
      "question": "When will an effect run if it doesn't have a dependency array?",
      "options": [
        "Only when the component mounts",
        "Only when the component unmounts",
        "The first time the component re-renders",
        "Each time the component is re-rendered"
      ],
      "correctOption": 3,
      "points": 20,
      "id": "6e49"
    }
  ],
  "highscore": {
    "score": 40
  }
}